{
  "quizzes": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Enterwell Quiz",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "kratko pitanje?",
          "answer": "Ada Lovelace"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "name": "bbb",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "bbb",
          "answer": "bbb",
          "id": 2
        }
      ],
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "mmm",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "kratko pitanje?",
          "answer": "Ada Lovelace"
        },
        {
          "question": "ddd",
          "answer": "ddd",
          "id": 3
        },
        {
          "question": "iiii",
          "answer": "ooooo",
          "id": 4
        }
      ],
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "novi kviz",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "iiii",
          "answer": "ooooo",
          "id": 4
        },
        {
          "question": "hfdgfd",
          "answer": "gfdgfdgdf",
          "id": 6
        },
        {
          "question": "lll",
          "answer": "lll",
          "id": 2
        },
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "kratko pitanje?",
          "answer": "Ada Lovelace"
        }
      ],
      "id": 4
    }
  ],
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "kratko pitanje?",
      "answer": "Ada Lovelace"
    },
    {
      "question": "lll",
      "answer": "lll",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "ddd",
      "answer": "ddd",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "iiii",
      "answer": "ooooo",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "pitanje",
      "answer": "odgovor",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "hfdgfd",
      "answer": "gfdgfdgdf",
      "id": 6
    }
  ]
}